{
    "subject": "Sarah_Clarke",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Xander_Berkeley",
    "human_readable": "Sarah Clarke is married to Xander Berkeley.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9433261752128601,
            "question": "Are Sarah Clarke and Xander Berkeley in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9212726950645447,
            "question": "Is Sarah Clarke married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9080821871757507,
            "question": "Who is Sarah Clarke married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9028497338294983,
            "question": "To whom is Xander Berkeley married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8752470016479492,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Sarah Clarke and Xander Berkeley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8257147073745728,
            "question": "Does Sarah Clarke have a husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7474788427352905,
            "question": "What is the name of Xander Berkeley's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7283922433853149,
            "question": "Are Sarah Clarke and Xander Berkeley known to each other?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7223082780838013,
            "question": "What is the name of Sarah Clarke's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6593742370605469,
            "question": "Who is Xander Berkeley?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sarah Clarke is married to Xander Berkeley.",
            "html": "yago_6946_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Sarah Clarke's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_6946_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are Sarah Clarke and Xander Berkeley known to each other?",
            "html": "yago_6946_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Xander Berkeley's wife?",
            "html": "yago_6946_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6946_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6946_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6946_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6946_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6946_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6946_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6946_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6946_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6946_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6946_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Sarah Clarke has been married to Xander Berkeley since 2002, supporting the statement that Sarah Clarke is married to Xander Berkeley."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}